police.it 2019-04-29

# Privacy Policy - Information for visitors (Art. 13 GDPR)

        Privacy Policy - Information for visitors (Art. 13 GDPR)
   In compliance with the EU General Regulation on the Protection of Personal Data UE
 679/2016 (GDPR), through this information note ("Privacy Policy") De Rigo Vision S.p.A.
      (hereinafter also referred to as "De Rigo") explains to visitors of the Websites the
    purposes and methods of processing personal data as well as indications on how to
                                        exercise their privacy rights.
By using our services you accept that De Rigo processes your personal data as described
                                            in this Privacy Policy.
                                                WHO WE ARE
First of all, De Rigo is a family with a fascinating history, to be told
and shared. Synonymous of experience, reliability and
resourcefulness. Founded in 1978 on the initiative of the brothers
Ennio and Walter De Rigo as a small artisan company in the
Belluno area, today De Rigo is one of the world leaders in design,
production and distribution of high-quality high-end eyewear, and
among the most important retailer in the field of international
optics. The Group's products are distributed in approximately 80          De Vision Rigo S.p.A. with
nations around the world, using 16 commercial branches, 4 retail            registered office in Z.I.
divisions and over 100 independent distributors.                         Villanova in Longarone (BL).
This privacy statement is valid for all visitors to the website
www.policelifestyle.com, as part of the personal data provided by        From 1978 we share a point
the latter to De Rigo.
                                                                             of view: excellence in
As part of the processing of personal data, the Data Controller is                  eyewear.
De Vision Rigo S.p.A. with registered office in Z.I. Villanova, 12
32013 Longarone (BL) - VAT IT01001050259, in the person of its
legal representative. In case the person concerned had requests
regarding this privacy policy or, more generally, the methods of
processing their personal data, please contact the Data Controller
at the address: privacy@derigo.com
                                  WHY AND WHAT DATA WE TRACK
In light of the services offered, the purposes for which De Rigo will
process your personal data are:
     -   manage back office activities for visitors to Internet sites
         (requests, support, claims, etc.)
     -   advertise the products and the brand managed by the
         company;
     -   improve the quality of the products and services provided
         by De Rigo.
                                                                          We want to share with you
                                                                          the main evolutions of our
As regards the treatments aimed at direct marketing towards
                                                                           brand and to make your
visitors of the website, interested parties will be required to
provide explicit consent. As regards the remaining purposes of the            browsing experience
processing, constituting a legitimate interest that does not affect         effective on our website
the rights of the interested party, it is not required to De Rigo to
gather explicit consent.
Considering the purposes described above and the type of services
offered, De Rigo will treat the following types of personal data

provided to the extent necessary by the interested party:
    1. common personal data, such as your personal details, your
         residential address, your telephone contacts or your e-mail
         address;
    2. navigation data, also known as cookies, such as the IP         To do this in the best way,
         address from which you connect to the internet, your login   we will treat your personal
         data, the type of browser you use or the queries from
                                                                     data, but only in compliance
         online searches on our websites.
                                                                              with the law.
Personal data are collected on an optional basis or on a mandatory
basis. If it is mandatory to provide personal data, these will be
flagged accordingly. In the event that an interested party refuses
to provide the personal data that De Rigo has indicated as
mandatory, we will not be able to process your requests.
                                       HOW WE USE YOUR DATA
In order to achieve the purpose for which we need to collect your
personal data, we will collect and store in our systems your
personal data from you spontaneously released and / or collected
from third-party sources. Your data can be collected and archived
also in paper format.
                                                                        We will keep your data
Your data will be processed by our operators, appropriately trained             securely
to carry out these treatment activities.
                                     HOW WE SHARE YOUR DATA
Your data, to achieve the above purposes, may be transmitted to
third parties, whether they are Autonomous Owners or External
Responsible for processing.
The categories of third parties that may be involved in the
processing of your personal data are:
    1. IT service providers;
                                                                      We may transmit your data
    2. Service providers that support De Rigo in its marketing
         activities;
                                                                     to third parties, especially to
                                                                     service providers we support
    3. Our sales network or other companies of the Group, if
         functional for the evasion of Your requests..
For the purposes described above, De Rigo can transmit personal
data collected to suppliers based in non-EU countries; in any case,
De Rigo undertakes to ensure an adequate level of protection by
setting appropriate guarantees in compliance with the GDPR
Regulation (EU 679/2016).
In the event that the third parties act as external managers of the
treatment, it will be the responsibility of De Rigo, to ensure that
these subjects process your data in an appropriate and secure
manner, depending on the specific treatment.
To ensure that this happens, De Rigo will make sure that the third
party presents appropriate measures for the treatment and will
provide the latter with precise instructions, while supervising its
work.

                              OUR OBLIGATIONS AND YOUR RIGHTS
OUR OBLIGATIONS
The data supplied by you or collected from third-party sources will
be stored in our archives to the extent necessary and only for the
purpose of pursuing the purposes described above.                          We will minimize the
                                                                        retention of your personal
To be sure to process your personal data in accordance with your
                                                                                     data
wishes, in any commercial message we will give you the
opportunity to easily express your desire not to receive further
communications from us.
YOUR RIGHTS
You have several options for managing your personal data that you
will give us.
Specifically, you can:
     •   Delete your personal data [ex Art. 17 GDPR]: you can         We will delete your data as a
         ask us to delete your personal data (for example, if you no
         longer need our Services). This request can be made to
                                                                          result of your request
         privacy@derigo.com
     •   Change or correct your personal data [ex Art. 16
         GDPR]: you can independently modify your personal data
         through the features present in each newsletter we send.      We will correct your data as a
                                                                       result of your request
         You can also ask us for changes, updates and data
         corrections, especially if they are not accurate, through
         privacy@derigo.com
     •   Limit the use of your personal data [ex Art. 18
         GPDR]: you can ask us to limit the use of your personal     We will limit the use of your data
         data, this request can be made to privacy@derigo.com          as a result of your request
     •   Right to access, receive and / or transfer your
         personal data [ex Art. 15 e 20 GDPR]: you can ask to
         access your personal data stored by us and to obtain and /
         or have your personal data transferred in a readable
         format. To advance this request you can write to us               You can withdraw your
         privacy@derigo.com
                                                                         consent to the use of your
     •   Opposing the use of your personal data [ex Art. 21                           data
         GDPR]: you can ask us to stop using all or part of your
         personal     data,  this   request   can   be    made    to
         privacy@derigo.com
     •   Right to make a claim [ex. Art 12 e 13 GDPR]: if you
         believe that your rights have not been respected, you will
         be able to lodge a complaint with the competent Authority        You can request access,
         according to the instructions published on its website          receipt and / or transfer of
         www.garanteprivacy.it                                                      your data
